





Role: System Admin

Industry: IT-Hardware & Networking

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: incident management, access management, servicenow, itil process, application support, exchange server, sccm, Office 365, intune, IAM, Identity Access Management, Access Management, IDM, User Provisioning, Microsoft Azure, Azure active directory

7 Zare,7 Zare douve directory

Verified : Le Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 19-Jan-21 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

### Summary

An enterprising IT professional with a course in Bachelor of Science (Information Technology) having over 5.7 years of experience in NOC, Networking, Access management, User provisioning & SAP. Worked in Network operations center tools like SOLARWINDS, Dynatrace, Database server monitoring, Backup job monitoring, Opmanager tool, New relic, Service Now, Appwork tool, CIM management and ITIL process. Possess good analytical and troubleshooting skills while having demonstrated talent for implementing and managing IT setup.

### **Work Experience**

MIPL as Senior analyst - IAM Dec 2017 to Sep 2020

Senior IT Analyst seeking roles in An enterprising IT professional with a course in Bachelor of Science (Information Technology) having over 5.6 years of experience in Access management, User provisioning & SAP. Possess good analytical and troubleshooting skills while having demonstrated talent for implementing and managing IT setup.

- HCL as IT analyst NOC & IAM Apr 2016 to Oct 2017
- Polaris & Intellect as Technical Support Engineer Jan 2015 to Dec 2016

Technical support engineer

^ Back to Top

#### Education

UG: B.Sc (information technology) from Indian Institute of Integrated Science and Technology in 2014

^ Back to Top

## IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
Opmanager, Solar winds, New relic	
Service Now, Appwork, CIM management	
ITIL Process	
Active Directory	

# 1

## **Important**

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

/ Suro Birodory		
SCCM		
Identity Access Management	0	5 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
User provisioning	0	5 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

^ Back to Top

## Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Tamil				

^ Back to Top

## **Affirmative Action**

## **Work Authorization**

Category: General Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.